

KRISHNADAS M.V Graphic Designer

Mylikara House **Desom, Aluva** Desom P.O., Ernakulam Kerala - 683 102

⊗ 854 777 458 0⋈ gdkrishna67@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I have 13.5 years experience in graphic designing in ad agencies, 1 year experience in a web designing firm at Kalamassery and 1.5 years experience in office works in ad agencies at Kochi.

I have excellent time management and organisational skills, accuracy, understanding of the latest trend, proven competence in design and professional approach to work.

I have knlowdege in work co-ordination, websites designing, digital works, logos, brochure, flyers, Psd file export to html, interactive pdf file creation, rollup standee designing, facebook promotion ad, etc,.

Age: 51 years

Date of Birth::4-2-1967 Marital status: Married

Relegion: Hindu

Cast: Viswakarma - Carpentar (OBC)

Passport No.: H7167968 Valid upto: 12-05-2020

RESUME

EXPERIENCE

Jelitta Advertising Co., Kochi → Dec. 2016 - Present **Graphic Deisnger - In-Charge**

Websites design - UI, Mobile App design, Facebook ad works, Paper advertisements, Brochure, Logo designing, client co-ordination, Intractive PDF creation, work follow up.

Maestro Tech, Kalamassery ➤ Sept. 2015 — 2016 Oct. Graphic Deisnger - In-Charge

Websites design - UI, Mobile App design, Facebook ad works, Brochure, Logo designing, client co-ordination, Intractive PDF creation.

Jelitta Advertising Co., Kochi ► Sept. 2009 - Aug, 2013 **Visualiser**

Brochure designing, Logo designing, Paper advertisments.

Mantra Communications, Kochi → Jan. 2005 - Sept. 2009 Sr. Graphic Designer

Work supervion, Brochure,, Logo design, Paper ads, Printing works

Media Mate Advt., Kochi ► Nov. 2000 - Dec. 2004 Graphic Designer

Brochure, Logo designing, Paper ads., Printing works

EDUCATION

High School Education | Pre-degree completed HTML, CSS - course completed

SKILLS in

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

CorelDraw

Presentation Skill

Visualisation Skill

Client Managing Skill

LANGUAGES

English – Read and write; Malayalam – Read, write and speak

...... R E F E R E N C E S

GIMMY THOMAS

Managing Parnter
Jelitta Advertising, Kochi
Mob: +91 94470 10329

ROHITH

Web Developer
Funriders India, Kadavanthra
Mob: +91 89431 89995

TOME GEORGE

Accounts Supervisor FCB Ulka, Kochi Mob: +91 98464 30942